flatpanelshd.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy policy - FlatpanelsHD

### Privacy policy

FlatpanelsHD is collecting anonymized data for statistical purposes, and personal data limited to your email address and sometimes IP address, if you consent to sign up to our newsletter and/or forum.

In addition, our partners may collect data used to target advertisement on and beyond flatpanelshd.com. When in the EU, we ask you to give your consent to the type of data that is collected.

We store data for as long as it can be useful, for example to send out newsletter and keep your forum profile active. If you stop visiting flatpanelshd.com, retract your consent, decide to unsubscribe from our newsletter, and cancel your forum profile, we no longer store personal data.

You have the right to request full details on the type of personal data that FlatpanelsHD has stored.

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy. In the case of significant changes that affect your experience of using flatpanelshd.com, we will inform you accordingly.

#### What we collect (cookies)

When you visit flatpanelshd.com, we collect anonymized data for statistical purposes (Google Analytics and Tag Manager). This data helps us gain insight into how our readers use flatpanelshd.com. No personal data is collected through this process.

In addition, we may collect personal data. This is limited to your email address and sometimes IP address, if you consent to sign up to our newsletter (MadMimi) and/or forum (phphBB installed on our server). When you sign up to our user forum, you decide which email address to register. In the case where you use a socal media account, you consent to share your email address and link the profile to your social media account. No data is other than the fact that you have linked your social media account to our forum for login purposes weill be shared with the social media network.

FlatpanelsHD is using cookies for these purposes. A cookie is a small code file stored on your device's storage via a browser. Cookies are automatically deleted after some time but will be renewed every time you visit flatpanelshd.com. Cookies are used for: 

* Technical functionality, meaning user login. A cookie ensures that you do not have to enter your login credentials every time.
* Anonymized statistical purposes
* To serve ads via partner systems, including targeted ads and non-targeted ads

#### Services used:

 **Google Analytics (statistical purposes)**  
FlatpanelsHD uses Google Analytics for anonymized statistical purposes. 

**Google Tag Manager (click statistics)**  
FlatpanelsHD is using Google Tag Manager for anonymized click statistics. 

**DoubleClick (ad system)**  
FlatpanelsHD is using Google DoubleClick as its ad system. 

**AdSense (ads)**  
FlatpanelsHD is using Google DoubleClick to serve targeted ads. 

**Disqus (comments systems)**  
FlatpanelsHD is using Disqus as a comments system below articles. You can post comments anonymously or by creating a user account. Disqus has its own [**privacy policy**](https://blog.disqus.com/update-on-privacy-and-gdpr-compliance). 

**phpBB (forum system)**  
FlatpanelsHD is using phpBB as its forum platform. You are required to create a user account in order to post comments in the forum. No user account is required to read forum posts. You can check what user data we store in the [**user control panel**](https://www.flatpanelshd.com/flatforums/ucp.php). In addition, we store IP addresses for all forum posts as an anti-spam measure and in the server log. The IP address is never paired with other user data in the forum or any other system used on flatpanelshd.com. 

**Cloudflare (cache & CDN)**  
FlatpanelsHD is using Cloudflare as its server cache service. This ensures faster, cached access to the website and serves as a measure against DoS(Denial of Service) attacks towards the server. 

**Other cookies**  
When serving adds, these ads sometimes use cookies for retargeting (same ads outside of flatpanelshd.com). This will depend on the ad provider and ad campaign. If you live in the EU, you must give your consent before ads can collect data required to targeting and retargeting.

**Other data**  
FlatpanelsHD is sending out a newsletter 1-2 times per week. This is only issues to users who have given their consent and signed up to the newsletter. We only collect your email address for this purpose. We do not pair your email address with any other personal data collected through other means. At all times, you can unsubscribe from the newseletter by clicking the unsubscribe button in the newsletter received. 

#### Sharing of user data

FlatpanelsHD does not sell collected user data to third parties. FlatpanelsHD does not transfer collected user data to third parties or countries. 

#### Contact

This website:  
Flatpanels Aps (the data controller)  
Vejlegaardsvej 65B  
2665 Vallensbaek Strand  
CVR: 33638426  
Data Protection Officer: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
